I started taking this top, click on it, you
can say the quality, but the problem was
that the time for the
policy was not handed over, I get questions that
I am
in polythene, a
lot of people did
not even
think that if we want to increase the cover, then it
works on the quick
subscription, then
its cost is less,
but now as
people are getting a lot of cheesy and super top, there can be some
problem with the association, like I have seen a
very
disgusting quantity, at the same time, you
need to know that super top, what are the
things that you need to keep in mind, which you should
sign in here, superpower product, so this is the
same thing, we will talk about, fleeting disease-affected
policy, elastic, thank you, you need to be careful about
in your life insurance
policy before extending the term, I would
like to say yes, my name is Prince
Chiku, I am Sakshi, Financial Planner
& Company, call green leaf, thin, sixteen
years, I bring you this video so that
your insurance company's biography and
financial planning is being done, simply
slide and can be made because our company
This creating verification
extends towards the video. You need to be careful about
life insurance policies. Like I
told you about the super top-up
plan. For those who don't know what super top-up insurance is, the
question is, if you have a sentence about an orange, if
your best friend is a lipid-neutral person, then
you will be taking a super top-up loan.
It has a deductible limit. If you
take a deductible example, if your
best policy is ₹3, or you take a super top-up
loan of ₹10, which has a deductible
option, then select it means that the first real
life base insurance will be given, and the
super policy will be attached to it. Simple rights, but it is
important to know something about the super top-up plan. So, what are those
things that
we will talk about? We are talking about this
because it is not that
some plan is good or some plan is bad. The
point is that for your awareness, you should
know what is
covered in your policy, what are the restrictions,
what are the limitations?  So that you do not get any surprise at the time of claim and you do
not get disappointed that you have gone wrong, you
should know that before taking the plan, firstly the room
rent can be different, it
is a comprehensive plan, in the baseline there
may be no room rent limit in it,
but in the super top up it may be a
single room or whatever room rent
eligibility can be done as per the plans,
so it is important to decide the room rent
limit, so for example, if you are
holding the best policy of the file, on top of that the
super top up is for the first setting light, then
yours is said to be 5 lakhs, if you have decided to pay 5 lakh rupees in the hospital, then
there may be a limit in the room category,
which you did not have in 20 years, so
you can check what is the room rent limit in both,
secondly these are two different
policies, so there will be two different policies, so
two separate policies
of state for applicable, a super top up is
not a single policy, that you see in many places  It is said
that you get one crore super seven prime in
many places and every
insurance company has promoted it like
Bigg Boss, on top of that line, but 22
crore super sevak lal, it is important to know that it is
not a single policy, the combination note
policy is two policies, so two policies will be
proved and there will be two policy cards also, so
when you become the PM, you
should have both the things on it and if there are two then it is better to take it
from a health insurance company, that means
you already have a best policy running from one company,
now you can take a policy from a bike company,
but it is sitting that
both of you are soldiers, plain salt plain
because according to different, you are the owners of the country, the
super topper is the first woman, so it will be surprising
that one has to give the claim settlement letter to the other
person, so I am not less, sevak,
work will be easy for you, card waiting
period can be different, so fast but the
baseline thing is the waiting period, the
waiting period of your pre-existing disease,
specific swelling black ticking dance
open  You can check that the
waiting period for the best policy and super top up can be different.
Fourth, if these are different
insurance companies, like GSM companies,
both of them are not related to each other, then
what will happen in this is that the
cashless metro hospital of both can be different or if
you are
taking a Dupatta policy on top of that, then the title
network hospital of both can be different, that can be
in Suraj Prakash Hospital,
where you have got the thing that the top up is
not a possibility, then the cancer network
is different, so you should know this in advance
that both have decided but it can be done
by the company, so
you know that if I have decided in the country, then
definitely super top up will be next
because the insurance company is empowered
with that hospital, now the question arises whether
they should leave the baseline for a longer time
or should they take a lower base plan with super top up, an
amazing decision from this year, okay, so
I believe that the topic is
very Happy Sunday, always, but at the same
time, many people say 1 lakh
Take a policy of 2 lakhs, I will
suggest you not to do this because the Everest
cream size is absolutely fine, it
is relaxed from the side, even for small things, it
comes at a comfortable price of 5 lakhs and 7 lakhs, so at
least if your earthquake quality is of 10 lakhs, then
you should take a topper on top of that like an idli sandwich, if it is
your choice then at
least keep the best policy of your creation, on
top of that super topper candy tag Lord Supreme
Lord Shankar and work on it like that,
whatever you want to take, then the next
most important points, for this I
thought of making a video, what happened, the
old policy was running in Twenty20 for many years
and how was this policy earlier,
3 lakhs, 5 lakhs, 10 lakhs maximum, on
top of that we and Spain do
not need health insurance, but when the son came,
people saw that a single claim place
in test, the time for which is 10 lakhs and 20 lakh rupees, so
this is
not sufficient for us, so they took a super
policy because  DS College
Quit cigarettes C Super Tapke policies lead
was something else Write the opposition later so
policy years time is not there so for example
I would like to take that when we talk about water
Rajdhar right time to buy some water policy which is
ruled by industry month and will give 13
if possible then nothing leader soil
month if you take the policy then it is better
why it matters now let us see I will
find out from the net the best policy
its time is silent and its 20th January
2021 and ended December 2021 January to
December is the cycle of this year so policy Rafi will
run for one year from 1st January 2021 to 31st
December 2016 then in between super policy was taken
in Jain's mind from June 2018 to
ji's statue in the film new thirty
first met it is strongly shortened doer
karma in January-February-March-April so
whatever comes on interference from this means
30th date of birth  I remembered the
thirty first mate, they attack it forcefully, the
late crop insurance policy which came in
demand of March 30th, 2021 was the
financial year ending, it was shot and
₹5 lakh, ₹5 lakh, your best
policy will easily play, five
lucky limits of option are here, now we will definitely ask you,
you do not have any benefit
because the next question we will ask is the
next account, if the
policy has ended then will there be any death benefit,
we will
not do it, next is the sixth class, its
oil is July 2017, now you have the above policy,
it has ended, so what do you think, will it be applicable on the
above policy or not,
because it is annual aggregate
deductible, that means
your 5 lakh deductible should be used in the policy, only then
that policy superpower will end, then you
can claim from it, of your super polythene
inch and file path in it
When the file was dutiable today, the doctor palsa, then 5 lakh should have
ended in the same year but it was the
year of super top up, 5 lakh from June, so whatever
ended got absorbed in the last year, so
here the insurance company has only one
way, see the film, the amount above 5 lakh,
in the last total, it will not take up to 5 lakh, that
means when 5 lakh dutiable is over, then
super top up at dubua, so what you thought that when
my 5 lakh is over, then I will be able to
take it from the super top, then that will
not be possible, many
people do not do this, if I have taken the super policy on a different date, then it is that
some portion will come, I have
put the country's money on the super top, then how will it be clean, then
that is the salary, valery question,
Someshwar, that your same month or graph is going to be
taken quickly, the enemy is going to take it in his hand first
when the policy is renewed, take it with the same, nothing like it,
if you have already taken it, have made
this thing clear that you have played a different role, then the
solution is that the credit policy is
ladies because super top  The cost of this is
not very high, you have to
take an excise policy at the place where you have your renewal
and with this policy you will quickly reach
Chopta Valley, the best
updates of this policy, here the cycle is life, the
preferred police should take your dupatta policy in mind,
this process happens in the previous degrees
in the policy where the
waiting period of specifications and images has to be
cleared if medical is possible
because in many conditions it will happen that it was not
reached at that time, right now there are some other medical
conditions for which you cannot take the policy, please have the
label, if you are eligible then please see the solution,
take the preferred policy and the old
preferred policy which is running here from June, continue it
till your
waiting period is over, so to
hit here, that is why on the old college
answer, if it is in that policy and till then the
policies have not been made for 2 years,
after that you will get that cycle fixed, if there is a
base in the border and a
super top in the semi, then this is its solution
From my side, I want to tell you about the super top side,
what is that thing
for which you need to fail, it is
famous to talk about all this in the morning that you should be fully vaccinated, not talking about that you should
not take this combination, you should not take this,
I am just talking about
how you should like your policy, what is it
necessary for you to know
what is a tree, you have many
questions outside, Radhe, you want to take a polythene,
so click on disturb, you
can buy a policy, that problem was there, that is why
to 9 and 10 friends where so many and
happy to advance that when I get
questions from people, I mean people actually
Gokharu positive wedding, after
reading the complete policy wedding, the discussion happens with me,
I like it, I mean how many
information people are taking benefit, how many
illegal will I take with it, so like level
means how many Avengers have I taken till date in the last two years,
see the substance master,
in the last one and a half years, write the Avengers, which never existed
before, how much premium is to be paid, check the amount, I have given the cheque  What is
online payment, but people are still getting into the
details which is the key point, so you should find them, it is
like a knowledge game, you are becoming
aware yourself, keep the number in front of you so that there is
no problem at the time of cleaning tomorrow, the picture should be very good, so this was
like me, I don't have any questions about super topper, if you want to
share anything then it can help other people too,
please do it, if you want to contact us,
hit WhatsApp number and phone number,
our WhatsApp number and email ID are below, you
can contact in the comment section, you
can share your question, please give the
next which will be made from this and you will get this
reminder, please subscribe my channel if
you have not done the correction yet, tube Reddy,
right information, RTI time, meet
in the next video, take care, bye-bye, do it, it has happened
[music],
do it [music]